{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"2490f040-b4a0-422d-bac2-8dd1ad238b5b"},"exam":{"id":"c5a1c5c0-89e1-4afa-9714-436588d35661","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"el8zebxq-qo1d-az5o-l4lp-vmh132hnt1zd","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance guarantees attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US?","explanation":"A HIPAA certification attests to the fact that the AWS Platform has met the standard required for the secure storage of medical records in the US.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"},{"url":"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippa_(disambiguation)","title":"HIPPA or HIPAA"}],"answers":[{"id":"827ec26130c30cc52e3fb178e0ef505c","text":"FERPA","correct":false},{"id":"739f96badcfca6fd03c1e5b17971c9de","text":"HIPPO","correct":false},{"id":"393dceb94f2cac456fd53985a67d72b3","text":"HITECH","correct":false},{"id":"dba5359496e7ea71f51ce4da1ee614bd","text":"GLBA","correct":false},{"id":"d0a785d52ac4a841f7efdf0098d9ebd5","text":"HIPAA","correct":true}]},{"id":"a5451611-68c3-4cf4-bff8-1c6f1972757e","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following tools provides a view of the performance and availability of your AWS services based on your requirements?","explanation":"Although it's easy to jump to AWS Service Health Dashboard as the answer, it does not provide a personalized view of AWS services; it displays their general status. It's AWS Personal Health Dashboard that focuses on the performance and availability of your AWS services so that you can respond accordingly.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/personal-health-dashboard/","title":"Personal Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"75d9f1b00702b15999acd998c1d19880","text":"AWS Service Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":true}]},{"id":"wdbn1na1-vwoh-03r9-ogc9-1ol20ezabw11","domain":"tech","question":"You need to run your code, but you donâ€™t want to worry about provisioning or managing servers. Which of the following AWS services would you choose? ","explanation":"Lambda is a Serverless technology that allows you to run your code without provisioning a computing infrastructure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"2e31cdf7daad1ca06d6642765fa13252","text":"VMware Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false}]},{"id":"d58bf9f4-44f6-49b5-b204-5aa9d88e98eb","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is classified as an AWS Networking & Content Delivery service?","explanation":"API Gateway is the only service listed here classified as a Networking & Content Delivery service. It is used to create APIs to access AWS Cloud or other web services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/apigateway/latest/developerguide/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon API Gateway?"}],"answers":[{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":false},{"id":"947642228a6d69446c74618fdde1bfd6","text":"Storage Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":false},{"id":"2ef9dd82927a3196ca2df3fc0cdf2e0b","text":"API Gateway","correct":true}]},{"id":"ej2zjxm0-a6xk-q2af-mol8-3c9zwje8qxyh","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support plans features a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system?","explanation":"Both the Business and Enterprise support levels offer a < 4-hour response time in the event of an impaired production system. Developer is < 12-hour response time in case of any system impairment. Basic does not offer any support for system impairment. Individual is not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false}]},{"id":"i9b6xlrs-qiap-mdwa-l2pv-m72run0d25np","domain":"security","question":"When considering the security of an AWS EC2 instance, which of the below are Users responsible for?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, users are entirely responsible for the security, patching and maintenance of AWS IaaS services such as EC2. AWS will only take care of the underlying hardware used to provide the service. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"51f337ee03b5fc05c3edf7764c0633b1","text":"Physical and Environmental controls","correct":false},{"id":"b6b41cd6bd59164805860b107633ce14","text":"Patching and maintenance of OS & Applications","correct":true},{"id":"6485477a46494966f254ee5c23dd8ba7","text":"Patching and maintenance of server hardware","correct":false},{"id":"8dee4c58b0c64b645b2052b129768b98","text":"Security Configuration","correct":true}]},{"id":"qlfvvg3n-igqt-be79-1bph-rx4nrjmqmm25","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below statements are correct in relation to security responsibilities in AWS?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud - the security of components that run the cloud service. The customer is responsible for security IN the cloud -- that is, the security of their AWS resources and data.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c5f3942078ece3769cd1bcbde2bdabb","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"a1b79685a2bbdb6743277416ad663c24","text":"As an AWS customer, you are responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"0369ed76a5e4ccb3887e44fe8a7c8703","text":"AWS is responsible for the security IN the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d1f8c47a806feef1c562619b465cb202","text":"AWS is responsible for the security OF the cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"sf55l98e-bpq0-sh7t-wkah-ex19vhdc9bie","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support services do all accounts receive as part of the AWS Support Basic tier?","explanation":"The AWS Support Basic tier is the free support given to all AWS Accounts. All accounts receive Billing Support, because every customer needs an avenue to lodge disputes, or make requests around their billing. 24x7 Support, Architectural Support, and access to a Technical Account Manager are all elements of paid plans.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7703baf6849325c6dd9df112e8b4b85","text":"Billing Support","correct":true},{"id":"30c247eb11a68c65f4625c0a83e97cdb","text":"24/7 support via phone and chat","correct":false},{"id":"4e88de53dbfa7fddf03f15ad5fd53eec","text":"Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"6ef823966f6d09ca49ae0117fbeb6f17","text":"Architectural Support","correct":false}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true},{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true}]},{"id":"hmh7tnlm-n4hf-9v8o-75e5-uksbwqwddinx","domain":"tech","question":"For which of the below is S3 a suitable storage solution?","explanation":"S3 is object storage suitable for the storage of 'flat' files like documents, photos, etc. Use cases which require very atomic or consistent reading and writing, such as databases and operating systems, are more suited to EBS (Elastic Block Store) storage.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"f28128b38efbc6134dc40751ee21fd29","text":"Documents","correct":true},{"id":"ea2ef9b0d095bf991f4973633b485340","text":"Databases","correct":false},{"id":"aab338915e32b60e92c8de3a23aa5c5d","text":"Operating Systems","correct":false},{"id":"b11ddc7e1671c0bd22dc89dd757508d4","text":"Pictures","correct":true}]},{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true},{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false},{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false}]},{"id":"nncwnx24-taau-zgsd-blel-newfprz6u93i","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to security?","explanation":"The AWS Cloud includes many design patterns and architectural options that you can apply to a wide variety of use cases. Some key design principles of sound design when it comes to security include: Apply security to all layers, enable tracability, and implement the principal of least privlidge options.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/apn/the-5-pillars-of-the-aws-well-architected-framework/","title":"The 5 Pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework"}],"answers":[{"id":"718831eabf7a4582f906032cd06bcea7","text":"Implement the Principle of Least Privilege","correct":true},{"id":"214beb729ce64f08fe84798c5bbedd6f","text":"Enable traceability.","correct":true},{"id":"ff94370d49b79e8817f49bbbc97dbf02","text":"Apply security to your application only.","correct":false},{"id":"d0f7903229df2e315b9c9561f18a4b7c","text":"Secure your physical resources.","correct":false},{"id":"4bb4d3eefe3829a2b20a099180702f9f","text":"Apply security at all layers.","correct":true}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false}]},{"id":"cf545dc9-39ca-4eec-869f-0d416b59aa1f","domain":"concepts","question":"Adding resources to your application as user demand grows is an example of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, it allows you to expand out as needed - as detailed in the question. Automation relates to simplyfying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although elasticity (the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) is related, this question specifically ask for in in response to user demand, which is closer to Scalability. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"3617c0aa-2fa9-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"For enhanced technical support, some AWS Support plans enable you to have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases. Which of the following choices offer this feature?","explanation":"With either the Business or Enterprise support plan, you can provide have an unlimited number of contacts that can open an unlimited amount of cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false}]},{"id":"9pyttsq9-bl16-280g-vfrs-2qkodijvmrmg","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are valid ways for an IAM user to manage AWS resources?","explanation":"The two types of access are AWS Management Console access and Programmatic Access. Programmatic access is available via the AWS API, the CLI, and the SDKs - and an IAM user can use all these methods. Security Groups control network traffic to EC2 instances, and do not provide access to managing AWS Resources. Emergency Access is not a feature of IAM.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/UsingIAM.html","title":"Controlling Access to Amazon EC2 Resources"}],"answers":[{"id":"2558c4af417f61e5475cc6e21268dd5b","text":"Emergency access via Identity Access Management (IAM)","correct":false},{"id":"8a49c0263f565565dafd85b396e5779a","text":"Security Group access via the AWS command line","correct":false},{"id":"8f12104b24647e69720266d8744a70c1","text":"Programmatic access via the command line","correct":true},{"id":"4d2e898f57bc396b4f79b35d5cc7a4c1","text":"Using the AWS Software Developers Kit","correct":true},{"id":"2fbca8dcca63ba9048e556de831897b1","text":"AWS Management Console access","correct":true}]},{"id":"3t2ov1u1-nwtz-6899-vmu9-eui5f3olrp6l","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allow you to make entire buckets (like one hosting an S3 website) public?","explanation":"Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets, whereas Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/example-bucket-policies.html","title":"Bucket Policy Examples"}],"answers":[{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"5a804d2999d40df9fee58c79e96c4bc6","text":"Bucket Policies","correct":true},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false}]},{"id":"b419a913-a5f1-4ad2-8c06-3b579643d073","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS responsible for in the Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"AWS manages security of the cloud. This includes the infrastructure, which consists of regions, edge locations, and Availability Zones. On the other hand, security in the cloud is the responsibility of the customer. Therefore, AWS is not responsible for safeguarding customer data; the customer is.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true},{"id":"0b4219abe92a5981f2c74b7a4ec441ab","text":"Customer Data","correct":false}]},{"id":"h0bz8vyv-zk25-7xf6-p1l3-v0qntk7m5yjw","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are types of cloud computing deployments?","explanation":"The three types of cloud deployments are: \r\n Public - where everyone and anyone can access that cloud's resources \r\n Private - also called on-premises where the underlying cloud infrastructure is owned and operated by a private entity for the sole use of that entity \r\n Hybrid - which is a mix of both. \r\n Mixed cloud is not a term used to describe a cloud computing deployment","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"7d22e2d665f6d51244a33f26e96904f9","text":"Mixed cloud","correct":false},{"id":"761883c0d5c55fba5b200ac8ac0d86e5","text":"Public cloud","correct":true},{"id":"2dde6ce98c19e445f3c47a7a9d166f04","text":"Hybrid cloud","correct":true},{"id":"cb38b39495aded16d3565297386a9c9e","text":"Private cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"0c9f823e-8368-41f9-a5e5-6dbdb7a5d728","domain":"tech","question":"You are creating an S3 bucket called company-subsite-logos, and you want to give it the exact same settings that your company-logos bucket has. What would be the quickest way of doing so?","explanation":"You can choose to select the company-logos bucket to pop up a screen and take note of all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket. However, it is easier to simply Copy settings from an existing bucket when creating a new S3 bucket.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/user-guide/create-bucket.html","title":"How Do I Create an S3 Bucket?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2833d56dbb85269cf9923f871b958148","text":"Select the company-logos bucket to pop up a screen. Write down all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket.","correct":false},{"id":"b3fc5f32c491e7a2f3414331506cd224","text":"At the Create bucket screen for the company-logos bucket, choose Copy settings from an existing bucket option, and then choose the company-subsite-logos bucket to copy its settings.","correct":false},{"id":"8dcfff9aa976530e7cb39a3561f8e013","text":"Right-click on the company-logos bucket. Write down all the settings in the screen to use for the company-subsite-logos bucket.","correct":false},{"id":"a4a7f2e73dfc3676b384b8e28e1b2447","text":"Create the company-subsite-logos bucket. Then right-click on it, choose the Copy settings from an existing bucket option, and then choose the company-logos bucket to copy its settings.","correct":true}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true}]},{"id":"b04194cb-7c18-41fd-af07-af547fcdf3df","domain":"security","question":"A consulting firm is conducting a Sarbanes-Oxley compliance audit of your IT operations. The auditor requests visibility to logs of event history across your AWS-based employee expense system infrastructure. Which AWS service will record and provide give you the information you need?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail provides visibility to API call activity for AWS infrastructure and other services. AWS Cloudwatch Logs might be part of a centralized logging solution, but all API event information will come from CloudTrail. AWS Systems Manager can process EC2 logs only, and AWS Compliance Manager is not a service offered by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/?nc2=h_m1","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"811708e04896b95951b61e58635cc92d","text":"AWS Compliance Manager","correct":false},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":true},{"id":"28408acf54ab04fe847fd24957e528d9","text":"AWS CloudWatch Logs","correct":false}]},{"id":"719cc66e-ayev-f5lb-zoet-xaar4i1a3kub","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following EC2 options is best for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns?","explanation":"Reserved instances are the most economical option for long-term workloads with predictable usage patterns - in this consumption method, you commit to using resources for a period of time for a reduced cost. On-Demand is great for when you don't have predictable patterns as you only pay for when you are using the resources. Spot works when your workload is interruptible and doesn't need to be available all the time.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/","title":"Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances"}],"answers":[{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"ead2a4026c18cbaca9c93c0974c23f89","text":"Dedicated Host","correct":false},{"id":"bad26119751b8bdb0b46bff9a096f500","text":"On-Demand instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customersâ€™ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. Thatâ€™s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false}]},{"id":"16rz9iw6-s5av-nrg1-1gja-89cbrnwj8uco","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are storage services?","explanation":"VPC is a Networking service, and RDS is a Database service, leaving S3 and Elastic File System as the storage services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","title":"About EFS"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"1dbd7e466350bb810a3ea48be7668773","text":"AWS Elastic File System","correct":true},{"id":"6e11595bc7ccdbf672fefaababf72939","text":"AWS RDS","correct":false},{"id":"94a6c127c422f3501ac2fd0084ebbd25","text":"AWS VPC","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"c6jepoji-nqyo-0t96-juj8-ob2lymloevj9","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the AWS Assurance Program?","explanation":"Certifications/Attestations and Compliance with Laws and Regulations are cornerstones of the of the AWS Assurance Program.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Assurance"}],"answers":[{"id":"fc0d934854b825185d4ea2079edf68c3","text":"Compliance with Laws and Regulations","correct":true},{"id":"506afacef0a47cc7635b5cf0a3476c31","text":"Certifications/Attestations","correct":true},{"id":"de208db5a32df9befe2ed7f080863f9e","text":"Customer Testimonials","correct":false},{"id":"4dc626268903b46b79d0a76e0a989cf8","text":"Partner Validations","correct":false},{"id":"19d78b92947f957cca4c7698118fdb82","text":"Following industry best practices","correct":false}]},{"id":"aosxkeh9-qevj-zztz-qgkg-lo0glwr2ccoh","domain":"billing","question":"By default, when using consolidated billing, which of the below will the master paying account be able to do in the member account?","explanation":"By default, using Consolidated Billing only allows the master account to view the billing information from the member accounts - no access is automatically granted for users in the master account into the member accounts beyond this. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","title":"AWS Consolidated Billing"}],"answers":[{"id":"25e6de5387e3157c014e2c6f2b0e810e","text":"Make changes to resources","correct":false},{"id":"54e29f93505b20fe2cc8af1cce96a33b","text":"View any data stored","correct":false},{"id":"29f838d6149e7ff36b4692f879dbd0a3","text":"Grant access to member account to other users","correct":false},{"id":"3dbb078ea9c1eaf843d213ba217af3e8","text":"View billing information","correct":true}]},{"id":"vsrs40em-06ny-u7sl-hdn2-xstt497klvo3","domain":"concepts","question":"Generally speaking, what is the minimum number of Availability Zones per AWS Region?","explanation":"At least 2 Availability Zones will be publicly available per AWS Region, with most regions having 3 Availability Zones available. There are specific exceptions to this rule, such as the Osaka Local Region, which has only one AZ by design.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":true},{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":false},{"id":"eccbc87e4b5ce2fe28308fd9f2a7baf3","text":"3","correct":false},{"id":"a87ff679a2f3e71d9181a67b7542122c","text":"4","correct":false}]},{"id":"10c453b6-5a2e-4615-9042-6c6fc00a7724","domain":"security","question":"When talking about AWS security, what does \"Authorization\" refer to?","explanation":"Authentication identifies who is accessing the system and passes that information to the Authorization process, which in turn determines what permissions the user has in AWS. Although Authorization is a part of the process to log in to the console, by itself it it is not enough.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/manage-users/","title":"Managing Users with IAM"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"IAM - authenticated vs. authorized "}],"answers":[{"id":"2fd83b869d1e9b4e9cb436b10c4dd876","text":"Logging in to the console","correct":false},{"id":"0159ee609574fa72f3ce74e9f9acae98","text":"Evaluating what permissions a user has","correct":true},{"id":"14f566a413faf99b530a23db8794522d","text":"A user delegating access to another user temporarily","correct":false},{"id":"1f8db5b38e9eb894bac42c8cfcc958a8","text":"Identifying who is accessing the system","correct":false}]},{"id":"evaz1xrv-t8dc-4b8o-0z8b-k29mzh203trs","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers the assistance of a Technical Account Manager?","explanation":"Only Enterprise (the highest level of Support Plan) offers the services of a Technical Account Manager.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"8d5e7e72f12067991186cdf3cb7d5d9d","text":"Premium","correct":false},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"4f5e27aa-65cf-46da-9db4-42b569eb0d05","domain":"tech","question":"Your employer, a major digital media company, needs you to implement an AWS service that delivers its dynamic web content worldwide, relying on edge locations to improve latency. Which one of the following services should you pick to accomplish that?","explanation":"CloudWatch monitors AWS resources and applications, CloudTrail increases visibility into user and resource activity, and there is no AWS service named CloudConnect. It is CloudFront that functions as Amazonâ€™s content delivery network, which is a system of distributed servers for delivering web content to users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"Amazon CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"e45b2ed303bc7e3b63b82e4766fd7d8b","text":"CloudConnect","correct":false}]},{"id":"d54df537-f2ee-46a2-b1f4-2c115bdf2044","domain":"concepts","question":"Using Infrastructure as Code is a related of which cloud concept?","explanation":"Infrastructure as Code is a key implementation of Automation in cloud - using Infrastructure as Code allows to quickly and easily deploy and manage your environment without reliance on humans to complete all the tasks. Scalability is the concept that as cloud has essentially limitless capacity, and it allows you to expand out as needed. Elasticity is the ability to go up and down in resources as needed. High Availability relates to the ability of your application to withstand failures in Cloud Infrastructure.","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":true}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false}]},{"id":"17fcc4a6-5565-4904-b460-9b24bb2aeacf","domain":"tech","question":"An online education company has customers on four continents. They need to run software functions to customize offerings for students in various locations around the globe based on parameters that each student enters. Which AWS service will provide this capability with the highest performance efficiency?","explanation":"Lambda@Edge provides the capability to run Lambda functions at Edge Locations based on events generated by the CloudFront content delivery network, allowing customers to extend their web applications globally. Amazon Elastic Container Service and Amazon API Gateway would require implementations in each desired region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/edge/","title":"Lambda@Edge"}],"answers":[{"id":"0383d27e1438422d247bbe8ffedfe1d4","text":"Amazon Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"dfdfd742376f1e718ab36a8a1ee9143e","text":"Amazon CloudFront","correct":false},{"id":"b0ccdb01b1aaa83a9e1d8bfbbc9a741e","text":"Amazon API Gateway","correct":false},{"id":"6fbef310c7868421732a75c85c868f77","text":"Lambda@Edge","correct":true}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"8x0x6jdm-e0n1-0rb6-ibad-we2hbkuaxgvw","domain":"tech","question":"You need to store a collection of objects that can also be accessed from a different AWS Region. Which service should you use to do this?","explanation":"S3 allows you to access objects from anywhere in the world - as long as the appropriate permissions are set!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"7b242f9e-5541-40b9-94c3-ff760252f026","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following scenarios are examples of scaling an IT architecture vertically?","explanation":"To scale vertically is to increase the specifications of a single AWS resource as needed. For example, resizing EC2 or RDS instances for more CPU, memory, or network capabilities is scaling vertically. Adding more EC2 or RDS instances, on the other hand, is scaling horizontally because it involves the increase in the number of resources, rather than the increase in each resourceâ€™s capabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"67c96e88044c732523807882de714af3","text":"Adding two more RDS instances","correct":false},{"id":"4fd553484e87f00281d8e2d07df1c3ac","text":"Resizing an EC2 instance type from a1.medium to a1.xlarge for more CPU and memory power","correct":true},{"id":"d2ed8876ad5d876850ebcde76e28bd9f","text":"Adding two more EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"f9de222cea376a61a621e215c4daf0dc","text":"Resizing an RDS instance type from db.r5.large to db.r5.2xlarge","correct":true}]},{"id":"5h2eems4-whow-d044-2cp2-g3qhkjhzcl4q","domain":"tech","question":"You need to host a file in a location that's publicly accessible from anywhere in the world. Which AWS service would meet that need at the lowest cost?","explanation":"With S3, objects can be accessed from anywhere in the world via a public URL. An RDS instance is used for hosting databases. An EBS Volume requires an EC2 instance to be accessible, and would be more expensive than using S3","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true},{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false},{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false}]},{"id":"92196d52-1bd3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"How many elastic IP addresses can you associate with a running EC2 instance with no charge?","explanation":"An elastic IP address is associated with each AWS account, and they can be associated with a running EC2 instance at no charge. If you associate additional ones, you will have to pay for them.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/elastic-ip-addresses-eip.html","title":"Elastic IP Addresses"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c4ca4238a0b923820dcc509a6f75849b","text":"1","correct":true},{"id":"c81e728d9d4c2f636f067f89cc14862c","text":"2","correct":false},{"id":"e4da3b7fbbce2345d7772b0674a318d5","text":"5","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":false}]},{"id":"84676206-45b7-4b8d-b856-91c915e8d017","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS service usages is free for the first 12 months after signup for an AWS account?","explanation":"Upon signup for an AWS account, you get 750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month for the first 12 months.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"02cbe76727c54b36b3ff3915aa629fae","text":"25 GB of Amazon DynamoDB storage","correct":false},{"id":"159df35cfb0a136f46cbecfe096e2468","text":"750 hours of Amazon EC2 t2.micro instance usage per month","correct":true},{"id":"267c5706cefc5dc9fb06ecdab987b079","text":"1 million API Gateway calls received per month","correct":false},{"id":"af41413a0bb72142c1ce2257ac3a184f","text":"1 million AWS Lambda requests per month","correct":false}]},{"id":"2c5901f2-c18a-456c-8a19-5d2da6952cec","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, this includes all aspects of capacity management, therefore it is an AWS responsibility to make sure that they never run out of storage. Replication to another AZ is also AWS's responsibility in an applicable storage tier - note that the question asks for AZ replication - not Regional Replication which would normally be the customer's responsibility to configure. AWS is also responsible for managing data corruption and resolving it if corruption is detected - however if it cannot fix the corruption, or if data is lost, AWS bears no responsibility for the loss - therefore it is a customer's responsibility to make sure there data is backup up as needed - either though versioning in S3, or through 3rd party tools.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/faqs/?nc=sn&loc=7","title":"S3 FAQ - Durability and Data Protection"}],"answers":[{"id":"f5a4db96c8f945bbaddfca968bc66a00","text":"Replicating your data to another Availability Zone if redundancy is needed","correct":false},{"id":"18e8e0efaea5ce9a47da52086c745de7","text":"Making sure there is enough physical storage available for your data","correct":false},{"id":"caec507833650a0d1b82cc852d15ea1f","text":"Backing up your data","correct":true},{"id":"96b64de5e30defc9bab2e6592e515b17","text":"Making sure that enough space has been provisioned for your data","correct":false},{"id":"f3cc93bd6eec33bc0d666a86175524cd","text":"Making sure your data is not corrupted","correct":false}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"b9e84187-a101-b202-89a5-c5882d80f712","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is a Shared Control of the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?","explanation":"Shared Controls are elements of the Shared Responsibility Model where both AWS and the customer have shared responsibilities within their own contexts. Patch Management is a Shared Control, since AWS is responsible for patching and fixing flaws within the infrastructure, including managed services like RDS, but customers are responsible for patching their guest OS and applications. Firmware Upgrades, and other Hardware maintenance processes are solely the responsibility of AWS. Configuration of Security Groups remain the responsibility of the customer","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"c57c1a92dac4991db4fa1bca1517cca0","text":"Hardware Maintanence","correct":false},{"id":"5d8e5aef41d3dab7bda43eaace3a2a06","text":"Patch Management","correct":true},{"id":"474eabe8590389108f1fc92c9435c405","text":"Security Group Configuration","correct":false},{"id":"9ce46290f3196adff1535137f5fc1ee9","text":"Firmware Upgrades","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true}]},{"id":"vikk5xb3-er5k-f530-xnql-upfbhr4zjhvv","domain":"concepts","question":"How many Availability Zones does each Region have?","explanation":"Normal Regions are made up of at least 2 Availability Zones to allow for highly available architectures in the cloud. The actual number of AZs can vary per Region.  There is a special class of Region called a 'Local Region' that have only 1 AZ, however that is viewed as an abnormal case by AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"61f2018e5a51be7a751ae1eb61c1f017","text":"Regions don't have Availability Zones, Availability Zones have Regions","correct":false},{"id":"32cf9ef8a3f23b762138a410b9f02129","text":"Only 1","correct":false},{"id":"57ca7c66f61abc17eb42ff90f5bed87e","text":"At least 2","correct":true},{"id":"f3f74d2863be40169cddca9e902304f3","text":"At least 3","correct":false}]},{"id":"ism9fl1z-nho7-nn22-5sn8-4qqdyyu4pyeq","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service?","explanation":"Lambda is AWSâ€™ event-driven, serverless compute service that allows you to run code without having to deploy or manage any of the underlying resources such as EC2 instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"f81195c4-7959-4925-a41d-e50f901cccad","domain":"tech","question":"Your System Administration team lead wants you to subscribe to the RSS feed to be notified of any interruptions to the EC2 service in the N. California and Ohio Regions. Which of the following will enable you to do that?","explanation":"Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, such as EC2, and it enables RSS subscription. The Personal Health Dashboard does provide information about the services you're using, but it does not give you the ability to subscribe to RSS feeds.","links":[{"url":"https://status.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Service Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"5b60dd28958c0d6d59a455cc074e4322","text":"Service Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"087edf830b5f3b392ebaef37ba8550f7","text":"EC2 Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"8e75b153e61c22a8ea4e14aadc7cb4ee","text":"Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"cf4db9f312542c8284a6ccdefcd98544","text":"Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"561b98dd-beb4-4111-8cb8-b5609a124873","domain":"tech","question":"What benefits can CloudFront bring to your e-commerce website?","explanation":"CloudFront provides the ability to cache both static and dynamic content in 200 points of presence located around the world, ensuring quick response times can be had by customers when retrieving cached website content. This inclueds protections with AWS WAF and AWS Shield. No additional analytics will necessarily be available, nor is CloudFront a database solution","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/features/","title":"Amazon CloudFront Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"3559eb841146fbbde9ede18594e319f1","text":"Protection against network and application layer attacks via WAF","correct":true},{"id":"61c592ef1e234bfa1834570f2238d22f","text":"Advanced analytics into customer journeys","correct":false},{"id":"bb42b85b5fcfff06d034f3102a1daa9e","text":"Lower latency for customers of your e-commerce website","correct":true},{"id":"286fe6e5d97e4ad18aac77cef2b5e28c","text":"Increased application availability","correct":true},{"id":"6c47d5971e79af6daf2b24070bd1e8ac","text":"Scalable managed database which integrates seamlessly with Lambda and EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"485886ee-d768-43eb-bf66-99dbf6ca890f","domain":"tech","question":"When might Auto Scaling be used?","explanation":"Auto Scaling monitors your applications and automatically adjusts capacity to maintain steady, predictable performance at the lowest possible cost.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"294a68b8b2e864aff39edf8b7b5ae662","text":"Where predictable workload patterns exist","correct":false},{"id":"653f92bb6e8a7e984815d88099db9ab2","text":"To control provisioning of S3 bucket capacity","correct":false},{"id":"4576fb5ff37cef52dcd4b0610521a97c","text":"When you require scalable capacity to maintain service levels in your environment","correct":true},{"id":"81a09fc79a5b8e06c0ba313f0c38b98f","text":"To provision resources that can be adjusted once per 24 hour period","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false},{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false}]},{"id":"c127gqer-wn02-ljaa-xx5a-jpsogr3yw2ij","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services are free to use?","explanation":"Whilst all of these services are free to use, the things they create or interact with can incur charges. For instance, a CloudFormation template is free to run, but if it creates an EC2 instance, you will be paying for that EC2 instance. Whilst some of the other services do have free tier entitlements or features, as a service, they do have general costs associated with them","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/services/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"caa58cad8d490fcdf1da0862623481fc","text":"Auto-Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"d85c80578ad0849a611c1056b63e385c","text":"VPC","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"prqyybkg-4flz-vdjf-hmny-u1q34ck87hm9","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are AWS compute services?","explanation":"EC2 and Lambda are AWS Compute Services, while RDS is a Database service, and SNS is an Application Integration service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":true},{"id":"54afc4697cf03d8e3ec9a05b16380622","text":"SNS","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"32c7f1bb-425d-4d33-b870-b88f89ef9f08","domain":"security","question":"An oil and gas utility company which is highly regulated must create a cloud governance scheme. The company is organized into multiple autonomous departments which will all be using AWS resources. These departments each sponsor independent projects that are reviewed by regulatory boards for the approval of customer price increases. The code and infrastructure for each project has production, development, and testing environments. Which of the following account strategies will maximize security and operational efficiency for the company?","explanation":"A multi-layered account structure will work best for this company, leveraging AWS Organizations to establish Organizational Units for each department, and separate production, development, and testing environments. While there is no physical AWS account at the department level, Service Control Policies can be applied at the Organizational Unit level, and billing can be reported separately for each department. An account for each department, in which the department combines dev/test/and prod, or a single account for the company hosting all workloads together will NOT provide for segregation of production, development, and testing environments at the account level. Multiple standalone accounts for each department and environment would compromise operational efficiency in managing environments across departments as there is no overarching AWS Organization to manage all the accounts centrally.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"AWS Security Best Practices"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","title":"AWS Organizations"}],"answers":[{"id":"6773420477c1653d8837f13bfa8ec24d","text":"Create a single AWS account for centralized security management","correct":false},{"id":"bb38e2c475c21f60a71674d4dd27ff93","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for each autonomous department within the company","correct":false},{"id":"281f961ca6e4d83f6570979548ba64e2","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for the production environment, one for the development environment, and one for the testing environment for all departments","correct":false},{"id":"e4be6081f1a5dc1cc67c1a4633121580","text":"Create an Organization Unit structure in AWS Organizations with separate underlying accounts for production, development, and testing environments","correct":true}]},{"id":"024e0354-7a25-4a81-b42e-ce2af844e0e5","domain":"security","question":"Which service might you use to provide Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection to your applications running on AWS?","explanation":"AWS Shield is a managed Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) protection service that safeguards applications running on AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1wf5g4cl-1eei-cxmu-red3-wkm59ywgq86h","domain":"tech","question":"With AWS Relational Database Service (RDS), which of the following are you responsible for?","explanation":"You are responsible only for the optimization of your application that uses RDS - AWS will take care of the rest as this is considered a Managed Service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"5f4dc8e976d91d69670d0a272e0ee6e3","text":"Database software installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"a514531b35c90598677ddee7c4b1afd9","text":"The optimization of your application using RDS","correct":true},{"id":"bc967dc2d57e6eff184a821bf7577a80","text":"Scaling","correct":false},{"id":"7b4eef372e52b848a7e0f93e59b06d70","text":"All of these","correct":false},{"id":"6bb1aca01fa54044f3ec9ae581b4620f","text":"Operating system installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"89f8bb80ca1403422295c6ad48f8cac7","text":"Database backups","correct":false}]},{"id":"b1acc5ea-cc62-4f91-9d0c-badb7c8ef957","domain":"tech","question":"You have been tasked with creating identical, repeatable Infrastructure for your customers. Which service will you use?","explanation":"CloudFormation provides the ability to provision a repeatedly deployable environment for your customers, CloudFront is a Content Delivery Network used to Cache content across the world. CloudWatch is used for telemetry and AWS Config is used to assess, audit and evaluate the configurations of your AWS resources.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true},{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false}]}]}}}}
